christianblog.com 2010-12-11

# ChristianBlog.Com Privacy Policy, Christian Blog, Christian Blogs, ChristianBlog.Com

| 

**ChristianBlog.Com Privacy Policy:**

The [ChristianBlog.Com Privacy Policy](http://www.christianblog.com/privacy.php) describes how we treat personal information when you use ChristianBlog.Com's products and services, including information provided when you use ChristianBlog.Com. In addition, the following describes our privacy practices that are specific to ChristianBlog.Com.

#### Personal information

  * ChristianBlog.Com asks for some personal information when you sign up to use ChristianBlog.Com, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.
  * In addition to publishing your weblog posts, you may also provide additional profile information, such as a photo, birthday, location, etc. and can edit your profile at any time on our [profile administration page.](http://www.christianblog.com/account/)
  * ChristianBlog.Com servers automatically record information about your use of the service, such as when you use ChristianBlog.Com and the frequency and size of data transfers. Information displayed or clicked in the ChristianBlog.Com interface (including UI elements, settings, and other information) is also recorded. If you are logged in we may associate that information with your account.
  * If you choose to use [ ChristianBlog.Com Mobile](http://mobile.christianblog.com/), we will record your phone number when you publish content, send a text message, photos, or SMS to or from ChristianBlog.Com. Your phone number may be associated with your ChristianBlog.Com Account or, if you do not have a ChristianBlog.Com Account, with some other similar account ID. We often generate this account ID based on your device and hardware IDs, so if you change your device or hardware, you will have to re-associate this new device or hardware with your account before we can authenticate you.

#### Uses

  * ChristianBlog.Com stores and maintains your account information and copies of your weblog posts and comments, including drafts, in order to provide the service.

#### Your choices

  * You can change your ChristianBlog.Com account settings, including your profile information, at any time in the Settings section of ChristianBlog.Com. You can edit, save drafts and remove your weblog posts at any time, as described in [ChristianBlog.Com Help](http://wwwwchristianblog.com/help/).
  * If you delete your weblog, we will remove all posts from public view. Because of the way we maintain this service, residual copies of your profile information and other information associated with your account may remain on back-up media.

#### More information

Further information about ChristianBlog.Com is available in [ChristianBlog.Com Help](http://www.christianblog.com/help/).

For more information about our privacy practices, go to [the full privacy policy](http://www.christianblog.com/privacypolicy.php). If you have additional questions, please [contact us any time](http://www.christianblog.com/contact/). Or write to us at:

> Privacy Matters  
>  c/o ChristianBlog.Com.  
>  P.O. Box 3206  
>  Eureka CA 95501 (USA)

Last updated: July 16, 2008

|   | 

**Donation Saturday:**

Every Saturday we like to remind our fellow bloggers that ChristianBlog.Com is highly dependant upon donations from our bloggers to help keep ChristianBlog.Com operational. If you have the ability to [donate a few dollars](http://www.christianblog.com/donate/) you can help keep this wonderful and awesome ministry website online! 

**Follow us on twitter!**

[@christianblog](http://twitter.com/christianblog) \- _our primary twitter account with tweets of all the latest published blogs!_

[@christianblogpr](http://twitter.com/christianblogpr) \- _our PR twitter account for releasing news and updates and such_

[@abelajohnb](http://twitter.com/abelajohnb) \- _the twitter account of the owner of ChristianBlog.Com_

---|---|---
